{
	"description": "Given names of Japanese girls",
	"deck": [
	{"question": "七海",      "answers":[ "ななみ" ] },
	{"question": "久子",      "answers":[ "ひさこ" ] },
	{"question": "久美子",      "answers":[ "くみこ" ] },
	{"question": "亜美",      "answers":[ "あみ" ] },
	{"question": "京子",      "answers":[ "きょうこ" ] },
	{"question": "佳奈",      "answers":[ "かな" ] },
	{"question": "信子",      "answers":[ "のぶこ" ] },
	{"question": "優奈",      "answers":[ "ゆうな" ] },
	{"question": "優子",      "answers":[ "ゆうこ" ] },
	{"question": "優花",      "answers":[ "ゆうか" ] },
	{"question": "優衣",      "answers":[ "ゆい" ] },
	{"question": "光子",      "answers":[ "みつこ" ] },
	{"question": "八重子",      "answers":[ "やえこ" ] },
	{"question": "典子",      "answers":[ "のりこ" ] },
	{"question": "凜",      "answers":[ "りん" ] },
	{"question": "勝子",      "answers":[ "かつこ" ] },
	{"question": "千代",      "answers":[ "ちよ" ] },
	{"question": "千代子",      "answers":[ "ちよこ" ] },
	{"question": "千夏",      "answers":[ "ちなつ" ] },
	{"question": "千尋",      "answers":[ "ちひろ" ] },
	{"question": "友美",      "answers":[ "ともみ" ] },
	{"question": "君子",      "answers":[ "きみこ" ] },
	{"question": "和子",      "answers":[ "かずこ" ] },
	{"question": "咲良",      "answers":[ "さくら" ] },
	{"question": "啓子",      "answers":[ "けいこ" ] },
	{"question": "奈々",      "answers":[ "なな" ] },
	{"question": "孝子",      "answers":[ "たかこ" ] },
	{"question": "幸子",      "answers":[ "さちこ" ] },
	{"question": "弘子",      "answers":[ "ひろこ" ] },
	{"question": "彩",      "answers":[ "あや" ] },
	{"question": "彩乃",      "answers":[ "あやの" ] },
	{"question": "彩夏",      "answers":[ "あやか" ] },
	{"question": "彩花",      "answers":[ "あやか" ] },
	{"question": "彩香",      "answers":[ "あやか" ] },
	{"question": "心優",      "answers":[ "みゆ" ] },
	{"question": "心咲",      "answers":[ "みさき" ] },
	{"question": "心愛",      "answers":[ "ここあ" ] },
	{"question": "心春",      "answers":[ "こはる" ] },
	{"question": "心結",      "answers":[ "みゆ" ] },
	{"question": "恵",      "answers":[ "めぐみ" ] },
	{"question": "恵子",      "answers":[ "けいこ" ] },
	{"question": "恵美",      "answers":[ "えみ" ] },
	{"question": "恵美子",      "answers":[ "えみこ" ] },
	{"question": "悦子",      "answers":[ "えつこ" ] },
	{"question": "愛",      "answers":[ "あい" ] },
	{"question": "愛子",      "answers":[ "あいこ" ] },
	{"question": "愛梨",      "answers":[ "あいり" ] },
	{"question": "愛美",      "answers":[ "まなみ" ] },
	{"question": "愛美",      "answers":[ "まなみ" ] },
	{"question": "愛莉",      "answers":[ "あいり" ] },
	{"question": "愛菜",      "answers":[ "あいな" ] },
	{"question": "成美",      "answers":[ "なるみ" ] },
	{"question": "敏子",      "answers":[ "としこ" ] },
	{"question": "文子",      "answers":[ "ふみこ" ] },
	{"question": "早紀",      "answers":[ "さき" ] },
	{"question": "明日香",      "answers":[ "あすか" ] },
	{"question": "明美",      "answers":[ "あけみ" ] },
	{"question": "昭子",      "answers":[ "あきこ" ] },
	{"question": "智子",      "answers":[ "ともこ" ] },
	{"question": "智美",      "answers":[ "ともみ" ] },
	{"question": "未来",      "answers":[ "みらい" ] },
	{"question": "杏",      "answers":[ "あん" ] },
	{"question": "杏奈",      "answers":[ "あんな" ] },
	{"question": "栄子",      "answers":[ "えいこ" ] },
	{"question": "桃子",      "answers":[ "ももこ" ] },
	{"question": "桜",      "answers":[ "さくら" ] },
	{"question": "楓",      "answers":[ "かえで" ] },
	{"question": "正子",      "answers":[ "まさこ" ] },
	{"question": "沙織",      "answers":[ "さおり" ] },
	{"question": "洋子",      "answers":[ "ようこ" ] },
	{"question": "浩子",      "answers":[ "ひろこ" ] },
	{"question": "清子",      "answers":[ "きよこ" ] },
	{"question": "照子",      "answers":[ "てるこ" ] },
	{"question": "玲奈",      "answers":[ "れいな" ] },
	{"question": "理恵",      "answers":[ "りえ" ] },
	{"question": "琴音",      "answers":[ "ことね" ] },
	{"question": "由佳",      "answers":[ "ゆか" ] },
	{"question": "由美",      "answers":[ "ゆみ" ] },
	{"question": "由美子",      "answers":[ "ゆみこ" ] },
	{"question": "百花",      "answers":[ "ももか" ] },
	{"question": "直子",      "answers":[ "なおこ" ] },
	{"question": "直美",      "answers":[ "なおみ" ] },
	{"question": "真央",      "answers":[ "まお" ] },
	{"question": "真由",      "answers":[ "まゆ" ] },
	{"question": "真由美",      "answers":[ "まゆみ" ] },
	{"question": "瞳",      "answers":[ "ひとみ" ] },
	{"question": "節子",      "answers":[ "せつこ" ] },
	{"question": "紀子",      "answers":[ "のりこ" ] },
	{"question": "純子",      "answers":[ "じゅんこ" ] },
	{"question": "結愛",      "answers":[ "ゆあ" ] },
	{"question": "結菜",      "answers":[ "ゆいな" ] },
	{"question": "結衣",      "answers":[ "ゆい" ] },
	{"question": "絵美",      "answers":[ "えみ" ] },
	{"question": "美代子",      "answers":[ "みよこ" ] },
	{"question": "美優",      "answers":[ "みゆ" ] },
	{"question": "美咲",      "answers":[ "みさき" ] },
	{"question": "美智子",      "answers":[ "みちこ" ] },
	{"question": "美月",      "answers":[ "みづき" ] },
	{"question": "美桜",      "answers":[ "みお" ] },
	{"question": "美穂",      "answers":[ "みほ" ] },
	{"question": "美紀",      "answers":[ "みき" ] },
	{"question": "美結",      "answers":[ "みゆ" ] },
	{"question": "美羽",      "answers":[ "みう" ] },
	{"question": "美香",      "answers":[ "みか" ] },
	{"question": "舞",      "answers":[ "まい" ] },
	{"question": "良子",      "answers":[ "りょうこ" ] },
	{"question": "花",      "answers":[ "はな" ] },
	{"question": "花音",      "answers":[ "かのん" ] },
	{"question": "芳子",      "answers":[ "よしこ" ] },
	{"question": "芽依",      "answers":[ "めい" ] },
	{"question": "茜",      "answers":[ "あかね" ] },
	{"question": "莉子",      "answers":[ "りこ" ] },
	{"question": "菜々子",      "answers":[ "ななこ" ] },
	{"question": "菜摘",      "answers":[ "なつみ" ] },
	{"question": "菜月",      "answers":[ "なつき" ] },
	{"question": "萌",      "answers":[ "もえ" ] },
	{"question": "葵",      "answers":[ "あおい" ] },
	{"question": "裕子",      "answers":[ "ゆうこ" ] },
	{"question": "裕美",      "answers":[ "ひろみ" ] },
	{"question": "詩織",      "answers":[ "しおり" ] },
	{"question": "貞子",      "answers":[ "さだこ" ] },
	{"question": "遥",      "answers":[ "はるか" ] },
	{"question": "里奈",      "answers":[ "りな" ] },
	{"question": "陽子",      "answers":[ "ようこ" ] },
	{"question": "陽菜",      "answers":[ "ひな" ] },
	{"question": "陽葵",      "answers":[ "ひまり" ] },
	{"question": "静子",      "answers":[ "しずこ" ] },
	{"question": "順子",      "answers":[ "じゅんこ" ] },
	{"question": "香織",      "answers":[ "かおり" ] },
	{"question": "麻美",      "answers":[ "あさみ" ] },
	{"question": "麻衣",      "answers":[ "まい" ] },
	{"question": "麻衣子",      "answers":[ "まいこ" ] }
]
}
